THEME SONG: In the not too
distant future, somewhere
in time and space, Mike
Nelson and his robot pals
are caught in an endless chase.
Pursued by a woman
whose name is Pearl,
an evil gal who wants
to rule the world.
She threw a few things in her
purse, and in a rocketship
she hunts him all
across the universe.
I'll get you.
I'll send him cheesy
movies-- oo-oo-oo--
the worst I can find--la-la-la.
He'll have to sit and
watch them all-- oo-oo-oo--
and I'll monitor
his mind-- la-la-la.
Now keep in mind, Mike
can't control--oo-oo-oo--
where the movies begin
or end--la-la-la.
He'll try to keep his
sanity with the help
of his robot friends.
Robot, roll call-- Cambot.
You're on.
Gypsy.
Oh, my god.
Tom Servo.
Check me out.
Crow.
I'm different.
If you're wondering how he
eats and breathes--oo-oo-oo--
and other science
facts--la-la-la--
just repeat to yourself
it's just a show.
I should really just
relax for "Mystery
Science Theater 3,000."
[slamming doors]
-Hi, everyone.
Welcome to the
satellite of love.
I'm Mike Nelson.
You caught us at
kind of a weird time.
See we're being dragged
back to this wormhole
by Pearl Forrester
and her minions.
We don't know where
we're going to end up.
-End of wormhole in sight.
Prepare for rapid deceleration.
[zoom]
[crash]
-Whoa.
-Oh.
-Oh, oh.
-Ah, come on, Mike.
Where did you learn that
little number from, Shatner?
-[laughs]
-What?
I just fell down.
-I mean, just overdramatic.
-Hey, a planet.
-Ah, great, yeah, some
new whacked out world.
You know, damn it!
I'm just not in
the mood this time.
-What is-- it looks like earth.
-Oh, but it's going to be
some weirdo parallel universe.
earth, where the only sentient
beings are zucchini, right,
huh?
-[laughs] No, all data indicates
that it is, in fact, our earth.
-Oh, yeah, sure.
But it's like a gillion
years in the future,
and super-intelligent koala
bears rule the planet, right?
-You know, that'd be kind of
cute, actually, little guys--
-Grow up, Mike.
-No, it's our earth,
in the exact time
we left it so long ago.
Hooray!
I guess.
-We'll be right back.
-Our own time?
Cool.
We can see Ethan
Hawke movies again.
-Yay!
-Hooray, yes!
-Maybe not.
I don't know.
-Wait, that's not a good thing.
No, that's bad.
[theme music playing]
-Giant dogs are probably
running the Department
of Transportation,
and I don't know what.
-Hey, look fellows.
Pearl's calling.
-Yeah, sure, right.
It's probably a turnip-headed
Pearl from the eight dimension
with tentacles.
-Give it a rest, now, Tom.
That's enough.
Come in, Mrs. F.
[thunder]
[wolf howls]
[whispers]
-Hello, Mike, Robots.
Cool place, huh?
I don't know where we are.
All's I know is that--
-Oh, Lordy, the rupture.
Bobo, don't play
with my luggage.
Set it down.
-Roger, whoa, oh, oh.
[crash]
[grunts]
-I somehow feel connected
to this place, Mike,
as if I have been
drawn here-- [voices]
by forces greater than myself.
Hey, shut up.
-I beg your pardon?
-Argh!
Don't do that.
And stop [slaps] with
the whispery hissing.
You sound like a
Brian Eno record.
-But it's not me, Pearl.
I'm sensing the presence of
several disembodied souls,
wandering these dark halls
in search of surcease,
an end to their endless night,
a howl of quiet desperation
towards an indifferent universe.
Nepenthe, Nepenthe.
-You are so gay.
-I could be wrong.
I don't know.
[thunder]
[organ notes]
[clunk]
[organ music]
[claps]
-Hey!
[organ music]
-Hey.
-I have never played before.
-[pants] Did I miss it?
Rock and roll, hey!
[organ sound]
Bobo, put a sock in it.
-Ok.
-Mike, robot pals,
in all my travels
throughout this
vast cosmos, never
have I felt so drawn to a place.
-Un-uh.
-It is as If I have come home.
[thunder]
[screams]
-I know now where
I am-- my ancestral
homeland, castle Forrester.
This is so freakin' cool.
Bobo!
BOBO: [inaudible]
-Quit clowning around and
bring my lab equipment.
All of it.
BOBO: [inaudible]
-Nelson get into that theater.
I've got things to do.
Brainpole!
-Yes, madame.
-[gasps]
-Oh, sorry.
-Send them a move.
-Ah.
-Something hurtful.
-[laughs]
-Something lancinating.
-Right.
-Searing.
-Ah.
-Excruciating.
-OK, then.
-Oh, something English.
-Ah, perfect.
Mike and little sidekick
pals, your movie this week
is a tepid little serving
of British cuisine, called,
The Projected Man
It's quite, quite bad.
[organ music]
-[laughs] [coughs] Sorry.
-Louis, Lou-i?
[beeping]
-Oh, mama.
-We gotta go.
-Ya, ya, ya, ya, ya.
[doors opening]
[music playing]
MIKE NELSON: [laughs] Ah,
oh hey, Faberge presents.
-The incredible
edible earth, ping.
-Oh, it's the end.
I guess we were late.
-Let's go.
-Yeah, right.
-I guess we'll go.
-No, stay right here.
-No such luck.
-Michael Tony and
Klinger Tenser present--
-So it's an orange with a
marble in it, locked in a vice.
-Huh.
-Right.
-With Mary Bryant
and Peach Haliday.
-Ok.
-Bryant Haliday, he's a
great [? fereli, ?] isn't he?
-Yeah.
-Nice.
Hugo.
-Versus the overhead
projected man.
-He's the guy other
people project
their inadequacies upon.
-Let's try something
in a green, good.
There, is that scarier for you?
-Featuring Heinz
Kidd and Scully Nor--
-Mike.
-Oh.
-Really.
-Sorry.
-Is this the "Rite of Spring?"
Should we be rioting,
right now? [laughs]
-The story of the AV Club.
-Just because you
show us a projector
doesn't mean we're convinced
there's a projected man.
-Stanley Pavey, big, stinky
crappy director of photography.
-BSC.
-Mm.
-Also starring Art, Peter,
second, Brian, assistant,
camera with editor,
Holding, Cooney,
Rider, Watkins, [inaudible]
-Come on, Mike.
It's not funny.
-(SINGS) I say, C. Cece Cooney.
Oh wait. (SINGS)
I say S. G. Ryder.
I say S--
-Oh, that's, that's funny.
-Oh, so it's my fault,
Mr. Brian Blamey.
-So far the continuity
lady's doing a real good job.
-OK it's an all skate now.
-Is this movie getting
its colors done?
-It's a mood movie.
-(SINGS) Project my love to you.
Projecting in your heart.
Ooh, I will project
my love on you.
[laughs] [sighs]
-Mike, we'll just torch the
theater and get out of here.
Come on.
-I'm with you.
-There, he's projected.
The end.
-Yay.
-Let's go.
[click]
-We're on.
-(HUMMING)
[brakes screeching]
-Hey, a jaunty jalopy.
-You want to watch
where you're going.
MIKE NELSON: [mumbles]
[revs engine]
-Pretty you may be.
-Um, he said pretty
you may be, ma'am.
I'm not sure what he meant.
-Uh, go past the drawings of
turkeys made out of kids hands
into Ms. Jenkins class,
-Um, driving she may be.
-Ah, parking, what
a way to establish
character and create tension.
-An exhaust system she may need.
[car brakes]
-Check this out.
She's wearing an entire
alpaca around her neck.
-I can't believe I have
to retake third grade.
-Ah, London.
[laughs]
-Were they worried that
this would be too top heavy?
Too much action at the
front of the movie?
[laughs]
-Will you be having
recess today, ma'am?
[door squeak]
-Well, bye.
CROW T. ROBOT: Bye now.
-They make cardboard rolls,
and that's all they do.
[typing]
[knock]
-Dr. Hill?
DR. HILL: Yes.
-Dr. Benny Hill.
-Professor Steiner
is expecting you.
I'm Sheila Anderson, the
department secretary.
Would you come in here, please?
-Follow my flip.
[knocks] Dr. Hill,
professor Steiner.
-Come in.
Come in.
-My ugly little dummy.
-Ah, it's wonderful
to see you again.
-And piggy to you.
-Well, cram it, you big--
-I do apologize.
On the spur of the moment, I
could think of no other code
name for you to give the guards.
-That wasn't what I meant.
-You haven't changed.
-Or taken a shower.
-Seeing you standing
there is as if the years
had suddenly dropped away.
-Oh, Paul, that was
a long time ago.
-Call me a pig again.
-What's the problem that
you want to discuss with me?
-I have a bad henna rinse.
-Swill for ya?
-Oh, thank you, Miss Anderson.
-And will be sex-- all, all.
[inaudible]
-Oh, Miss Anderson,
is Dr. Mitchell in?
-Yes, sir.
-Mitchell?
-He went into the lab.
-Would you ask him
to set up a test run.
I'll be along presently.
-At once.
-And bring some ham.
I love it.
-I'm working on the
conversion of solid objects
into pure energy.
-Uh-huh.
-Energy which can be stored
in a cell composition,
projected over long
distances, and then
turned back into
the object again.
[sigh]
-All kinds of objects.
-Yeah.
-Including human tissue.
-Ooh.
-Human tissue?
-Yes.
-Tissue.
-Now television,
television is one method
of transferring a visual image
from one place to another.
-But the image is
flat, two dimensional,
lacks life, and
needs a receiver.
-Like Cris Collinsworth?
-Where I've achieved
is the projection
of an object in three
dimensions, something
that has weight,
depth, and body.
-And orange hair.
-And without a receiver.
-So not like Cris Collinsworth.
-Yesterday, I achieved
my first projection
of a living creature.
-You're drinking it.
-Ew.
-Unfortunately, something went
wrong, and the subject died.
-But how long it live?
-Oh, two to three minutes.
I want you to tell
me why it died.
-Hm.
-Whether there was any change
in the cellular structure
during projection.
What I need to correct.
-Well, don't kill things.
-What's the principle
that you employ?
-Mr. Weatherby, as usual.
-I'll show you, come with me.
-We'll take the tube to
the Darby, hop the lift,
and see about my schedule.
-Eat it.
Go on.
Eat it.
Come on.
-Uh, Mitchell--
-Don't poke things in the thing,
-I'd like you to meet Dr. Hill.
She'll be joining
us on our project.
-You could say we'd met before.
-Well, almost.
-Uh, Mitchell is
an expert on laser.
-I'm afraid I know
very little about it.
-Oh, well then fit her out with
a heat suit, explain it to her,
and I'll go set up the console.
-There?
-Professor Steiner, I had
to tell Dr. Blanchard You
wanted another experimental run.
-Uh-uh.
-And?
-He's given his permission
on this occasion.
In future, he requires
24 hours notice.
-And you've been instructed
to see that he gets it.
TOM SERVO: [laughs]
-I have.
-You're an ugly,
stupid little doctor.
-Dr. Blanchard's the director
of this foundation, isn't he?
-Hm, you can say that again.
I'm in the middle.
-Caution, my filling is hot.
[laughs]
-You're were going to
tell me about laser.
Sorry.
Well, I expect you know
it's a way of overcoming
the scattering of light waves.
-Mm-hm.
-In its simplest form we
put an electric current
through a mixture of
neon and helium gases.
-Right.
-And when the light
and emitted, it
becomes a coherent
source of power.
-Sure.
-You mean it doesn't go
off in all directions.
-Exactly.
-Hey, listen up. [taps]
-One very narrow beam that can
transmit more signals than all
the television and radio
channels put together.
-Blah, blah, blah.
-It's light in a new form--
-Uh-huh.
-Which I have modified to
transmit matter itself.
-Are they suiting
up for NASCAR here?
[laughs]
[buzzing]
-Pasty labs, where
nothing is distinct.
[laughs]
-Now, I'd like to
demonstrate with something
of your own, Pat,
something you'd recognize.
-Your knickers, perhaps.
-My watch do?
-Couldn't be better.
Come with me.
-Well, actually, your
knickers would be better,
but that's fine.
-This is the
transmission cradle.
-Where your knickers
might have gone.
-It creates a massive
magnetic field;
-It's got a roll bar.
-Now, the watch.
-Knickers would be ideal, but
the watch, that's fine, fine.
Imagine sending your watch
three feet across the room
-Now put your visor
on and stand back.
But keep your eye on the watch.
-Major decisions,
knickers are bigger.
Still, your tiny, unseeable
watch is what we have,
and we'll at least make
the best of it, yes.
[theme music]
[buzzing]
-I'm going to kick in the
sheet metal cutter now.
Switching on the Evinrude.
-Releasing the cicadas now.
Hit the valveless trumpet.
-Wow.
-Hey, there's steel town
girls on a Saturday night.
-Hm.
-What do you know.
-Ow.
I'm fading, fading.
I was water resistant
at 30 meters.
I was a clam shells design, ugh.
-Could I at least
see your knickers?
-Duran Duran is going
to pop in now, right?
-Neat.
Do you have the time?
-What has happened at this
stage is that the basic matter
of the watch has been
transformed into pure energy
and is stored over
there in that cell--
-Uh-huh.
-Forever, if necessary.
Now, we wish to
transmit that energy
to project the watch, in fact.
-But since we can't, we'll
nip out and have a cuppa.
-Yeah, I really control
it and stuff. [laughs]
-I assume Dean Jones will
be in this eventually.
-Oh, yeah.
-Probably.
DR. STEINER: Laser preheat.
DR. MITCHELL: Laser preheat in.
-Grease and flower cake pans.
DR. STEINER: Laser
emission relay.
-Laser emission relay on.
-Bottom falling out of plot.
Movie sucks.
-Are we not blokes?
-Relay one.
Relay one in.
-Really dumb scene end.
[buzzing pitch rises]
-Relay two.
DR. MITCHELL: Relay two on.
[laughs]
-Ow, well, here come the dogs.
[barking]
-Project.
-Dispense soft serve.
-He probably just tosses
the watch over there.
-Oh, where was I?
-Now, we'll see what
happened to your watch.
-And then move on to your
knickers if you're comfortable.
-Tick, tick, [breathing heavily]
tick, tick, tick,
tick, [breathing]
tick, tick, tick.
-Still want it?
-That's incredible.
-I succeed every time
with an inanimate object.
If only I could do the same
thing with a living creature.
-Oh, keep that to yourself, man.
-Unfortunately, there's a gap
between the molecular structure
of metal and that of living
tissue, which I must bridge.
-What are these burns?
-Oh, well, that's something we
still don't quite understand.
It--
-Oh, look at the watch.
[winding sound]
-Kot-kit kot-kit,
kot-kit, kot-kit, kot-kit,
kot-kit, kot-kit,
kot-kit, kot-kit.
-Oh, would it possible
for the direction
of the magnetic field,
the polarity, to--
-No, we thought of that.
No.
TOM SERVO: [laughs]
-Change in projection?
-No,
-I suppose it could.
I've never really
thought about it.
DR. STEINER: Well, we better
start thinking about it
If this kind of
distortion is present.
No wonder the Guinea pig died.
-[gasp] Murderers.
They were using Guinea
pigs as Guinea pigs
-Oh, no, a shock.
Maybe there is
something in my theory.
Look what the shock has done.
-It's almost time for high tea.
-No human being could survive
a time transition of that kind,
not without fearful
consequences.
-Well, Wally down
in research survived
a time transition of
that kind one time.
-Yeah.
-Kramer!
Oh.
-Just returned from
safari with Lord Melbury.
-Who are you?
-I'm assisting Professor
Steiner, who are you?
-Dr. Blanchard, director
of this foundation.
-Well, then you should know
better than to startle me
when I'm focusing a microscope.
-Wow, can I look?
-Let me see your
identification card.
-Certainly.
-This is a classified division.
The work is secret.
No one is allowed in
without my permission.
DR. STEINER: She has permission.
Mine.
-I'm Mr. Rogers.
-Dr. Hill is working
here at my own expense.
-Even so, an arrangement of
that sort requires my authority.
-[mumbles]
-What name did you say?
-Dr. Hill.
Dr. Patricia Hill.
-Oh, old tin pants Hill?
-I'm extremely sorry.
Dr. Hill.
I apologize.
For a moment I
didn't recognize you.
-Maybe it's my overall
or the lighting.
--[chuckles] I'm sure
you'll be of great
assistance to Professor Steiner.
-She already has been.
With her help, I'm on the
verge of demonstrating
proof of my theory.
-I'm glad to hear it.
-I'll just get out of
the movie then, sorry.
-Oh, by the way,
Steiner, I hope Dr.
Mitchell made it quite clear
this morning that I cannot
agree again to
these demonstrations
being taken at short notice.
-Mitchell.
-[laughs]
-Quite clear.
-You see, I have to
warn other projects
that may be needed power.
These matters have to
be properly programmed.
-I said Dr. Mitchell
made your point.
-Good.
-I'll just turn
into a wolf then.
-Well, I won't interrupt
you any further.
Good day, Professor
Steiner, Dr. Hill.
-May I climb you some time?
-Please don't think the
foundation finds you unwelcome.
-Thank you, Dr. Blanchard.
-I'm just going to
visit my bow ties.
Cheerio.
-Paul, look at this.
-Oh, chipped a tooth on
the bangers and mash.
-Mitchell--
-Mitchell.
-I want you to regard
what I'm about to say
as highly confident.
-Yes, sir.
-I'm a shemale.
-Ooh [inaudible].
-Um, I've been instructed
that next Tuesday,
the ministry is sending
professor Lemback of the Geneva
Institute down to witness a
demonstration of Professor
Steiner's projection experiment.
-Professor Lemback, yes, sir.
-Hm.
Obviously, it'll be
necessary for you to know.
You will have
preparations to make.
But I would be
obliged if you didn't
mention the visit to
Professor Steiner.
-Hm.
-That is, for the time being.
But, Doctor Blanchard--
--[inaudible] Mitchell,
please, please.
-Shh hush lambkins. [laughs]
-There are reasons why the
visit should not be announced.
I will, myself, inform
Professor Steiner in ample time.
-In that case, why tell me?
-Well, you're my
sweet cookie pants.
-As I said, Mitchell, you
are my representative.
Not Steiner's.
That should be sufficient.
-I still don't understand.
-Don't make me go to the larder
and unseal a tin of whoop ass.
[door shutting]
-The right honorable
Sir David Cassidy.
-It's not going to be as
simple as we'd thought.
I had hoped that Lembeck's
visit would throw him,
but he seemed to be more
advanced than I'd imagined.
He's brought in a pathologist.
MAN: You're in no position to
allow anything to go wrong now.
-Yes, meow, you know.
Mm, yes, purr, then.
Mm-hm, yes, mm, meow.
DR. BLANCHARD (ON PHONE):
But what can I do?
My hands are tied.
You'll have to use your
position with the ministry
to delay the demonstration until
I find out how far he's got.
-Put it off?
-It's a mince off.
MAN (ON PHONE): After I
spent three exhausting days
heckling the minister
to arrange it?
-But you have to
accept that things
have changed in three days.
-The bickering explodes
across the screen. [laughs]
-He may have achieved
some sort of breakthrough.
I must find out before
any official demonstration
could possibly [inaudible].
-I'm quite uninterested,
really I am.
-[mumbles]
-That demonstration will
take place, but it will fail.
Steiner must be discredited
in front of an official party.
-Ah, good one, man, yeah.
Right on.
DR. BLANCHARD (ON
PHONE): [inaudible]
possibly make sure
that he will fail.
-If not, there are certain
aspects of your warm and cozy
private life that suddenly will
become much more widely known.
-All right, all right.
MAN (ON PHONE): Good,
we're agreed then.
-[laughs]
MIKE NELSON: So what do I
do with this thing again?
Oh, right there, yeah.
-Warm and cozy private life--
does he know of my strolls
by the ducky pond and my
Sunday visits with Mummy?
-Bite down.
(SINGS) Overture,
light the lights.
ALL: [hums]
[buzzing]
-OK, now cut that
Styrofoam with a saw.
-Fire up the leaf blowers.
All right, tease
the howler monkeys.
-And they are making
so many keys in there.
-Yes, the same thing
you've seen before,
only it's happening again.
--[laughs] Hey, hey I was
called in as a consultant.
Wait, you said you
needed my opinion.
What are you doing?
-Wow, is she breastfeeding
him all of a sudden?
What is she, Tori Amos?
[beeping]
-Big boxes of spare monkeys
up there on the shelf.
-Yep.
-I'll have to do a more
careful examination--
-Yeah, use gloves, all right.
---but I think I can pronounce
the patient fit and well.
-Oh, that's splendid.
Congratulations.
Hey, don't I get a kiss too?
-Why certainly, Chris.
Oh, you mean from her.
I'm sorry.
-You know, it needed
such a tiny adjustment
to counteract that time phase.
-Well, there's
nothing to prevent me
from calling the ministry and
arranging a demonstration.
Chris, get the glasses.
I think we deserve
a celebration.
-This is really
going to embarrass--
-Oh, blah, blah.
-Now don't be too harsh on him.
After all, it's
his job, and we're
not one of his pet projects.
-You're too generous.
-Blanchard hasn't spoken to you?
-About what?
-We have to buy our
monkeys from Sam's Club.
-Well, if it's something that
concerns us all, tell us.
-It's supposed to
be confidential.
He's arranged a demonstration.
-He's done what?
-For Tuesday.
The Ministry are bringing
Professor Lembach.
He told me days ago and
ordered me not to tell you.
-What does he expect to gain?
-I can't believe
it unless he's so
childish he thinks
he can embarrass me.
-The bloody Darby.
-Chris, don't tell
him you told me.
Don't even tell
him we've succeed.
-Don't even ever
talk again ever.
-I'll be childish
too and surprise him.
-And off on an odyssey
your class ring
goes projected from
here to another reality
living a new life.
-Yeah.
-Really?
You really transported it?
You kno-- I mean, it's
not just, you know, gone.
-Oh, like Servo and I don't
know what we're doing.
Duh, we just through
this projector together.
-Hey, uh, what you got
in your hand there, Mike?
-Aw, oh, no, not this.
This is my St. Blaise medal.
My grandma gave it to me.
It protects me from all
ailments of the throat.
-And it will continue
to protect your throat,
only it will be doing
it someplace else.
-Yeah, let's give it a shot.
-Well, OK.
If you're sure.
-Slap it down.
-Again, transported molecule for
molecule, um, someplace else.
-Right.
-Where?
-Oh, around.
Now, Mike, have you got anything
else we could project, please?
-I don't-- oh,
well, you know what?
I do have these, these
love letters from Denise.
She, uh, she wrote
all of these right
be-- right before she,
uh, before she died.
-Right, before she died.
Come on.
Throw them down.
Yeah!
-Woo hoo!
There they go.
-You know what?
If I didn't know
better, I'd think you
guys were just burning the
things that mean the most to me
and thinking it was funny.
-You know though, I can see
where you'd think that, Mike, I
want you to know
it's patently untrue.
-Yeah, what he said.
Now what else you got?
-I'm fresh out you
guy-- Oh, you know what?
I do have one more thing
that may serve your purpose.
-[inaudible]
-Wow, that one really
meant a lot to me.
-I'll bet it did.
What was it?
-Uh, Tom's autographed
picture of Shirley Jones.
-Hey, wait a minute.
No, no, oh, Shirley!
-Take it easy, Tom.
It's not like it's gone
or something, right Crow?
-That's absolutely right, Mike.
-We'll be right back.
-Oh, for fun.
-Ah, we have fun around here.
-I'm tremendously excited
over this pivotal space.
-Shirley Jones.
-Eh, well, it's around.
-In some ways, I think it's a
pity [inaudible] the job is.
It couldn't have been
delayed, Professor.
I'm sure Steiner would prefer
to demonstrate at a later date.
-There are urgencies.
-[mocks accent]
-It's not so urgent
[inaudible], but my dear friend
and colleague here assures me
my visit will not be wasted.
-Ah, sieg heil.
-Sheila?
We also drink will
only stand and wait.
-Then don't stand or wait.
-Eh, shot out of
the saddle again.
-Ever notice how unpopular I am?
-That's quite a
performance of Blanchard's.
If only he knew what
was in store for him.
-Oh, please.
Think you're not
part of all that?
Paul's very grateful to you.
So am I.
-Ugly dummy.
-You knew him very
well, didn't you?
-Look I'm trying to drink here.
-I worked with him
once in Stockholm
soon after I qualified.
-She wacked with him?
-I guess.
-You're sure I wouldn't be
treading on anyone's toes
if I asked you to
have dinner with me?
-No.
-I won't go, but.
--[inaudible] but that was
all finished a long time ago.
-Projected man!
Yeah!
-It's a remarkable
development, Paul,
but I don't
understand how you've
overcome the time element.
-Oh, well, you will very soon.
-Shall we start?
-Mitchell?
Check that everything's ready.
-Yes, Professor.
-Eh, I was about to
get shot down anyway.
Women hate me, you know.
-Padded doors, they
matches in here, or?
-Where would you like to go?
-Just, I'd rather
Paul didn't know.
-But I thought you said--
-I did, and I meant it.
It's, oh, I don't know.
He's on edge.
I wouldn't want to do anything
that would precipitate--
-Excitement or plot development.
-[inaudible]
-Uh, what's that got to do with
me taking you out to dinner?
-Nothing, really.
It's just him and his
work I'm thinking about.
-So it's popcorn and girls at
the big 10 for me again, huh?
-In here, Professor Lembach.
-Thank you.
-Turn me down anyone?
Anyone wanna turn me down?
-Ready?
-Ready.
-This will be fun!
He he.
-Dr. Hill will show you the
subject for the first part
of our demonstration,
which is the transfer--
-What?
---the subject into stored--
-I can't--
-Please watch the
subject carefully
when I give the signal to--
-Freedom!
-You know, despite all my rage,
I'm still just a rat in a cage.
-Uh, I think the dryer's done.
-Let's project the
hell out of this rat.
-[inaudible].
-Wow, a lot of
blood in that rat.
-[inaudible]
-Wait, almost ready.
Just cleaning up.
Groom, groom, groom.
Gotta keep clean here.
Hang on.
Heh.
-Because I can, by the way,
if you must know the answer.
-You guys know you're
turning me invisible, right?
I mean, you're the humans.
I assume you know what
you're doing here.
-Hello?
-The animal now is in the
form of pure energy, which
is stored in that
cell over there.
I will now project the
animal on to the target tape.
-What?
Nothing in here.
---the timeline element--
-Huh?
---which caused death in
our early experiments.
Please watch a target table.
-Yes, no more tedious
carrying rats across the room.
-Laser preheat.
In.
-Laser remission [inaudible].
-Laser--
-Go on.
---on.
-[inaudible]
-Or better relay two.
-Relay two.
-Ugh, I have to go.
-OK, you're really
scared of new situations.
-Action old guys.
-Cut the power!
-Cut the power that be.
-By mistake he cut the cheese.
-Geez, India must
be so embarrassed
to have been ruled
by these twits.
-Yeah.
-Got some clotted
cream in the car.
-I wish this was "Cheech
and Chong's Up in Smoke."
-Eh, all's I know is I hope
this movie has a good vent hood.
Gonna need it.
-Power line to the story cell
is completely burned out.
Just like depriving
the brain of blood.
Now it's completely destroyed.
-So we can't project the rat?
-He's gone wherever
good rats go.
-What was Mitchell
ever thinking of?
-Why?
What's it got to do with him?
-Maintenance.
It's part of his function.
Perhaps he's just
loyal to Blanchard.
-Paul, that's unfair,
and you know it.
-I don't know anything anymore.
-Just makes my hair all orange.
-What about Blanchard?
Have you seen him?
-Oh, he ran off with
Lembach and that man,
Latham, like a scolded cat.
Well, you must explain.
We must try and
arrange another--
-Paul?
-What do you want?
-You parked me in.
-[inaudible].
-Well, it's a bit
late for excuses.
-Oh, Paul, please.
-I'm not making any.
Look at this.
-They're burned through.
That's hardly surprising.
-Look at the leads.
-Well, they're burned through.
What should I expect?
I specifically told you
to check everything.
-I did.
You still can't
see what's wrong?
-Ya pumpkin haired ponce.
-Those are acid burns.
-Sabotage.
When the power built up, the
natural heat in the wires
completed the rupture.
-So we bought a truss.
-I'm surprised we
weren't all killed.
-I'm disappointed by it.
-Who would want to
do such a thing?
-Somebody who wanted to
make sure the experiment
was never completed.
-Well, it doesn't
make any difference.
It'll be months before
we can be ready again.
-But I can replace
this overnight.
-You can't replace
the story cell.
Without it the
apparatus is useless.
-I think it's only shorting.
-Shut up, and get orange hair.
-What if you're right?
Then we can recharge it.
-I'm darn sure we can.
-How long is Lembach staying?
-I'll find out.
-The tension!
How long is Lembach staying?
-I'm afraid this takes
precedence over dinner.
-You see, I love Lembach.
-Chris, what does it mean?
Well, the idea that somebody
would want to destroy Paul's
discovery, well,
it frightens me.
-Well, if that was
their intention,
they certainly
haven't succeeded.
If we work day and night,
get the apparatus in order,
achieve another
perfect projection,
we can convince everyone
including Blanchard.
-Then the movie will
be off and running.
-Right.
Well, I could always
do with a [inaudible].
-Lembach is staying in
London for another few days.
-Yay!
-Hooray!
---for me to have dinner with
him at Blanchard's house.
-Well, then you'll be
able to convince him.
-Yes, but someone seems to
be trying to prevent me.
-Paul, that's the
voice of despair.
I'm sure we can get
it in order again.
-Do you think so?
-Yes, I do.
-Yes.
-If I stand here talking,
I'll never even get started.
-Oh, Pat.
-What if something leads to the
premature departure of Lembach?
-I wish I could be
fully sure I trust him.
-Why shouldn't you?
-You're the only one I
have faith in now, Pat.
Don't desert me.
-What do you mean?
-He's paid by the
foundation, not by me.
-I thought he was
paid by the hour.
-Oh, [inaudible].
-I've been watching both of you.
-From the bushes.
-Be very careful
before you go too far.
-Before I doff my
knickers, you mean?
-Paul, you're tired.
I think you ought
to go home and rest.
I'll call you as
soon as he's ready.
-No.
I have to be sure
that I'm ready.
-Why?
What do you have in mind?
-An idea.
Nothing more.
-I've got to go spot
clean the monkey.
-Backo.
-But I have succeeded.
-My dear Paul, this is
neither the time nor the place
to argue so vehemently.
-You tell him, my man.
-Now we sit
comfortably digesting
Dr. Blanchard's
excellent dinner.
-I am not arguing.
I am stating facts.
I have only to call my two
assistants who are waiting.
I can arrange a
demonstration tonight.
Now!
-Steiner, you are
behaving inexcusably.
-And in front of Lembach.
-You were only invited because
Professor Lembach wanted
to meet you again before
returning to Geneva.
-This is unfair.
My demonstration was ruined.
-Demonstrations
do go wrong, Paul.
I do not hold it against you,
but I cannot remain in London.
I'm needed in Geneva.
-My demonstration was sabotaged.
-[inaudible]
-It's true.
I have evidence.
This is my evidence.
-A solenoid?
-It doesn't take
a technical mind
to see the acid burns on
the ends of the connection.
-If there had been sabotage,
Dr. Mitchell would have told me.
-At my request, he did not.
Come with me, and
see for yourself.
-Steiner!
-Made you look.
-I had no intention of
telling you tonight,
but now you are forcing me.
Only this morning,
my committee decided
they have gone far enough.
Your experiment
will be abandoned.
Tomorrow you will start
dismantling your laboratory
to make room for another
and more urgent project.
-A second bathroom.
-I cannot accept your decision.
It's monstrous.
I've achieved success.
You cannot deny me
my demonstration.
-You have no choice.
-Lembach, do something.
-How long will you
gentlemen be here?
-For some time.
Why?
-Then I will give
you evidence that
will force you to
acclaim my discovery.
-Funding intrigue.
-I cannot allow my friend to
leave in this state of mind.
-Professor?
-There's cake.
-I think it would be
better to leave him alone.
-Were you not hard on him, Dr.?
It was not of my seeking.
And in any case,
he had to be told.
Under the circumstances, this
seemed as good a time as any.
-What were his
prospects of success?
-One in crap-dillion.
-Like most other advanced
experiments, limited.
[phone ringing]
Oh, the world is ending!
-Oh, it's just a British phone.
Ok.
-Wow, that was close.
-Hello?
Oh, Dr. Hill.
No, he isn't back yet.
-Not back?
Have you heard from him?
-No.
It's getting very late.
I can't stay much longer,
or I'll miss my bus.
-Who is it?
-It's Dr. Hill.
-Eh, well, too bad.
-Sheila, I need your help.
-Of course, Professor.
-All right, come with me.
Leave it.
-But it will be Dr. Hill again.
-I said, leave it.
-We're going to the
Cliff Richards concert.
-Was it Hill again?
Will Lembach stay?
-I want to know why Sheila put
the telephone down if he did--
-But he said he would call
as soon as he was ready.
-I think something's wrong.
I want to go back
to the laboratory
and find out what's happened.
-All right, all right.
I want to know
what's happened too.
-Let's just swing by Lembach's
and see if anything's going on.
-Yeah.
-Oh, hi.
Could you give me a lift?
I love it.
-Was that originally
built for squirrels?
My Uriah Heep compilation
tape is almost done.
-Man, VCRs were
complicated back then.
Wow.
Whew.
-I'm sure I'll never
get it right, Professor.
-Now don't be
frightened, Sheila.
When I raise my
hand, press this.
When all these lights
are on, press this.
-This is my tuxedo shirt.
Press this.
-[inaudible]
-The sound will then
die down and rebuild.
I programmed the
entire second stage.
All you have to remember is when
all these lights are burning--
-Press this.
-I understand, Professor.
-Now don't be frightened.
When this is all over, you
could tell your boyfriends
that you helped
trigger an experiment
that made scientific history.
-My boyfriend is Linus Pauling,
so I don't think he'll care.
-Ah,j forget it.
-Oh, oh, Sheila.
-Mm, yes.
-But first a song.
-He sawed hula hoops already.
-I'm doing it all
for you, Lembach.
-Now he'll come out half
man, half wristwatch.
-I'm gonna fax my butt
over to Lembach's.
-I like Ringo best.
-Wagons, ho!
-Mrs. Debbie Frankenstein.
-My fall is falling.
-Eeeeeeee.
-The golden arches.
He's McProjecting himself.
-Sheila!
Don't touch anything!
-D'oh!
She immediately
touches something.
-Excuse me while I disappear.
-He's trying to project himself.
Sheila's interrupted
the program.
-You know, even when stuff's
happening in this movie,
stuff doesn't happen.
-[inaudible]?
-Be my usual wooden
ineffectual self.
-I, I can't stop
the [inaudible].
-He knew that we'd
try and stop him.
[screaming]
-Hehehehehe, wipeout!
-OK, hero's gone, movie's over.
Let's go.
-Let's beat it.
-You know, at this
point I really
do have to agree with cutting
off the funding though.
Yeah.
-Giant nuclear
blackhead extractor.
-[inaudible].
-Petula Clark's
bedroom, here I come.
-Wait, there's a fly in there.
-Stop her, please.
-The abominable Dr. Sheila.
-No, that doesn't work.
-Eh, well, this just isn't done.
-Well, enough of the film.
Let's just sit in
the dark for awhile.
-Two luminescent
clocks were spotted
hovering over London today.
-Lembach?
Where are you?
-Lembach!
-It's a Bob Vila
Halloween special.
-Don't push it too hard.
We got plenty of time.
-Shut up.
We're only here three more
minutes, and we're done.
-I'll go take a look, see if
you've woken up the neighbors.
You get at it.
-I want some amontillado.
-I meant get at that.
There'll be time
for the other later.
-Oh.
-Who's that?
-[inaudible].
A cat, I expect.
-Never heard a cat
make a noise like that.
-You know, perhaps he
was having a bit of fun,
and she wasn't in the mood.
-Everything's an innuendo
to these Cockney gits.
-Keith Richards?
-Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's Keith Richards.
You're right.
-Ha.
Got a great furball worked up
and spraying left and right.
What a great life I lead.
-Oops, someone's
snapping cats over there.
-Hey, Gloria, what'd I tell you?
A flipping cat.
Relax, girl.
Relax.
-All right.
Oh God, I could do with a drink.
-You'll be getting
something more
than a drink when we
get through this lost?
-What is it with these people?
-Harry?
Is someone over
there by that mound?
I can see him moving.
-Go and take a look.
If it's a bloke, chat him up,
but keep him away from here.
-I think his
Cockney's a bit rusty.
-Yeah.
-Hey, it's a brick.
-Brick
-Hmm, from the Wonder
Woman line of footwear.
-Hello there.
-Got any salad cream?
-You got the time?
-Hey, I'm eating cat here.
[screams]
-He ripped her
London Times in half.
-Hey, what the bloody hell
did she scream like that for?
-How should I know?
-I'm just as dumb as you.
-I'll go and take a look.
-Hurry back, I get lonely.
-Gloria?
-G-L- O-R-I- A?
-In excelsis deo.
-Gloria?
-I hear they got your number.
-Come on, girl Wake up.
Don't much about.
-Yeah, yeah.
She's mucking about.
Laying there with no pulse.
She's been shocked to death
by a guy with a touch of death
who came through a time portal,
and she's mucking about.
[screams]
-Hey, Nelldorado.
-Shhh.
I'm talking to Lembach.
I'm going to try to
convince him to stay.
-Great idea.
-Cool.
It'll be so much better if we
can just get Lembach to stay.
-So cool.
LEMBACH (ON PHONE): Hello?
-Uh, oh, hi.
Lembach, say, this is
Mike, Crow, and Servo,
and we were just wondering
if you could, you know,
stay a little longer.
LEMBACH (ON PHONE): Well,
I really should be going.
-Tell him there's pie, Mike.
-Well, there's pie.
-And we're all going down
to Shenanigan's later.
-Right, Shenanigans.
So, so, will you stay?
LEMBACH (ON PHONE): Well, OK.
-All right!
Lembach is staying!
-You can't keep us down, Pearl.
Lembach is staying.
-Quiet, fool.
I found my ancient family
diary of the Forrester clan.
It's fascinating.
Ancient numbers for
ancient bookies.
Topaz Walling for
[inaudible] Forrester
really knew how to
play the ponies.
And here, 1000-year-old
malt liquor labels.
And an end to diluvian form
of chicken and a biscuit
called Her Majesty's
fools hen crackle bread.
What a rich and marvelous past.
What's this?
Apparently, my
ancestors have always
been involved in
odd experiments.
Amethyst Rogento-Forrester
trapped a man in a cave
and pushed in bad
paintings of the hunt.
Emerald Montgomery Forrester
trapped a man on an island
and forced him to read
poorly done parchments.
And, and could this be?
[? aventurine ?] [? salboda ?]
Ford Forrester trapped a man
in a tree and told
him really bad sagas.
It's incredible.
I have a feeling I'm on
to something here, Nelson.
Some mm, mm, mm, power.
Some force beyond my control.
And it doesn't
look good for you.
-Lembach, Lembach, Lembach.
-This doesn't matter, Pearl.
Lembach is stay--
[phone rings]
Hello?
LEMBACH (ON PHONE):
Yeah, this is Lembach.
I think I'm just
going to take off.
-What?
LEMBACH (ON PHONE):
Thanks anyway.
-No, Lembach!
-Aw, man.
Come back, Lembach.
Come back.
-Gloria?
-I suppose I should get
over there, say "Aah!"
and get bzzzed.
-Harry?
-(ENGLISH ACCENT)
It's no fun destroying
a wall all by meself.
-Where the hell are you?
-(ENGLISH ACCENT) I'm
here and I'm dead.
--[gasp] The death
of Steve Winwood.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT) It's the
Queen Mum, and she's nude!
[roar]
[buzzing]
-Joy buzzer of death.
-You know, on the bright
side, maybe he'll kill Oasis.
-You can only hope.
-He shouldn't have fallen
asleep on the Fry-Daddy.
-That side of his face looks
better than it did before.
-Crawlers, get your crawlers.
I've got five of them.
-Oh god, his shoes are horrible!
Ah!
I guess they're just a
littl scuffed, actually.
-Yeah, they're fine.
-Projected haggis
is more like it.
-Oh, his hair came out
looking pretty good.
-Yeah.
-He's going to check himself
into the Pond's Institute.
-What?
Pantyhose are on sale?
Three for $1.00!
Oh my.
-Hm, looks like
a sockeye salmon.
-Just needs a dab of Dermablend.
-You know, he could
just grow his hair long
and comb it over his ugly side.
-Yeah.
-SureGrip, because
they sure grip.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT) Now I'll
just knock up the chemist,
purchase a tin of salve.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT) Purveyors of
rubber gloves to Her Majesty,
the Queen since 1673.
-Oh, let's see here.
Epsom salts, witch
hazel, styptic pencils,
[inaudible] chrome, Queen
Helena's face scrub,
[? corn ?] [? plasters, ?]
tincture of iodine,
Gold Bond medicated powder.
Oh, and the industrial-sized
tube of Anusol.
[laugh]
-Well, I came in here
for rubber gloves.
I should just stick with that,
not go on a big buying spree.
-Yes, score!
And they're Isotoners.
Yeah!
-Uh, do you have these
in a grey kid leather?
--[laughs evilly] I'm
going to wreak revenge
and terror on--
oh, cute barrettes.
Wow.
-Uh, hey, you guys
sell fishing licenses?
-You know, I'd give
up half my face
if it meant being able
to break into drugstores
to steal rubber gloves.
-Sure, in a heartbeat.
-Is now the best time for him to
be doing is Tai Chi exercises?
-Hm.
WOMAN: Don't worry, dear.
I found a bucket on
the dressing table.
-Man, he's been
projected 10 minutes,
and already he wants to kill
everyone and everything.
-Yeah.
-Hi.
Say, hey, do you have
lemon swiss cream Maalox,
or just the mint?
-A SureGrip rubber coat!
Wow, what luck.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT)
This will all go
very nicely with
the rot on my face.
-Legalize it then.
Right-o.
-Ah, the movie finally
admits it's dead.
-Electrocution?
-You said I'd be gassed!
-But we-- we found them slap in
the middle of a building site.
There was no power
cables in 100 yards.
-Come and look.
The burns are typical.
[phone ringing]
-That'll be for me.
-Inspector Combover.
-It's Davis.
Ah, Martin, you got it?
MARTIN (ON PHONE): One
[inaudible] slinger.
The woman's Gloria King, which
must make the other Steve Lowe.
-That's got to to make quite
a hole in the road scary.
I'm sorry about old
Harry, though he
was so bloody bad at it.
What-- what were
they up to, exactly?
--[laugh] Of all things, digging
away into the [? furrier's. ?]
-He's so funny.
-So crude, they nearly
got away with it.
What's the picture?
-Uh, wait a minute.
Will I be able to recognize it?
No, no.
Don't bother.
Just run up a few relatives
to form identification.
The cause of death, I'm
told, was electrocution.
You better get
down there and see
if you can find
out any reason why.
-Electrocution?
-Yes, I know.
-Shocking, isn't it?
Hee hee!
-Oh.
-Sorry.
-Oh, Crow.
-Let's have a look.
-You chaps amaze me.
I've hardly finished
my examination,
and here you are,
putting names to them.
-Yeah, we amaze
ourselves sometimes.
-Ah, I just put them
in my junk drawer.
-That's low all right.
-Yup, very low.
Right down by the floor.
[laughs]
-Oh, now over here.
What-- I--
-And here's where I put
my dishes after I eat.
DAVIS: Well, well, well.
-Well.
-I've seen Harry in a
good many positions--
-Whoa!
-But I never expected
to see him in this one.
You silly old fool.
-Yes we'd gone through the "Kama
Sutra" together many times.
[laughs]
-She's a floor
model on discount.
-Now, this is one of my victims.
-I'd say she was scared, too.
-All three had a similar look.
-Business casual.
-Wow, kind of a combination
Buddy Sorrell, Bilbo Baggins.
-Well, after 50
years, I have to admit
that huge, long eyebrows
don't attract women.
-I thought that damned
Lembach would never go.
-What's on Steiner's mind?
-Something pretty
spectacular, if I knew him.
-Has he repaired the damage?
-Just guzzle my expensive
brandy, that's fine.
-I don't know.
He and Mitchell have been
working day and night.
-Those things are
like diving platforms.
-You ought to get your
hands on those tapes of his.
You're still sure they're
the key to his experiments?
-Yes, they are.
Yes, we should
get them to night,
before he removes them himself.
-Yuck, what is this crap?
-Yeah.
-We can get them now.
-But I'm drinking!
-We?
-Well, you then.
-I hardly think it's
my line of country.
-Well, I can't do it by myself.
-[gulping] Ah.
-They have a security man.
No, this is what we'll do.
-Drink, then drink some more.
-I'll drive into the
Foundation with you
concealed in the boot of my car.
-You'll be nude, of course.
-Um, I'll give you my keys.
-Then we'll drink.
-You'll find your way up
into the main laboratory,
help yourself to the tapes.
-Uh, have a nip.
-In the meantime, I'll take the
security men up to my office.
-Oh!
-And that way, no
suspicion will fall on me.
-But I've been dating
the security man!
-Oh, [inaudible] new
[inaudible], of course.
-Well, off to Sotheby's
to bid on a bow tie.
-Well?
-Let's go back a security man!
-Come on.
-[gulping]
-Yeah, I suppose I'll
shampoo my eyebrows later.
-[car horn]
-Out of the way,
you stupid gate!
-It's the border between
East and West England.
-I want you.
-Oh, sir, finally!
-We've been trying to get
you on the telephone, sir.
-Me?
What for?
-Yes.
It's Dr. Mitchell, sir.
He's waiting up in your office
with Dr. Hill and Ms. Anderson.
-Mitchell.
-There's been some trouble in
Professor Steiner's laboratory.
-Professor Steiner
is still here?
-Uh, well, he did
come in earlier, sir.
-Anybody in the laboratory?
-No, sir.
-Huh.
-[grunt] Very good, sir. [grunt]
-Did you want me
for anything, sir?
-Doesn't matter now.
-He always says
he wants me, then
it's just always
talk, talk, talk.
--[hums] (SINGING) Spanish
songs in Andalucia,
[? mandalina. ?] Oh, me
[inaudible]. [humming]
-Can't get used to driving on
this side, and I was born here.
-Hm, I was supposed to meet
my bow tie supplier here.
--[grunt] You could
your stinky gym bag back here.
-That's [inaudible] they
smuggled Morley Safer in.
[music playing]
-Tension music, you know.
It makes me tense, and
I want to hit someone.
-Now around this corner,
I change into Eyebrow Man!
-I want you, but not you.
-Well, it seems
just as well that I
decided to return tonight.
Even so, I find your
explanation pure fantasy.
-To me it makes sense.
-Elves did take him!
-He was obviously trying
to project himself.
-Into a different movie!
-The cross on the map,
he's exactly on your house.
With these calipers, he worked
out distance and trajectory
from the Foundation.
-Yeah.
-Graph bears me out.
-And you are seriously
suggesting that he
would materialize
himself in my--
-[mumbling]
-Perhaps not in your study.
But in your house, certainly
-[whimpering]
-Dr. Hill, I can understand
how upset you are.
But what you suggest
is illogical.
-There is nothing illogical
in what I am saying.
-Then tell me, where is he now?
MITCHELL: Can't.
Sheila unwittingly
disturbed the program.
He could be anywhere
in any state.
[crying]
-You don't have to
cry about it, sir.
Do we have to keep Sheila here?
She looks exhausted.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT) Poor
McCartney got married!
-[crying] It's my eyes.
They're hurting.
-I'm sorry, Sheila.
Maybe she should see a
doctor, or [inaudible].
I'll see to it.
It's past 2 o'clock
in the morning.
How will you get home?
-[crying] I can't!
-Well, look, look.
You just-- you just run to
your office and, uh, and
get those clothes off.
-Yeah!
-Yow!
-I'll see that your driven home.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT) Yes,
all of them off now.
Every stitch.
-[grunting]
-Oh, she's Professor
Paul Steiner.
I was mixed up.
--[grunts] Must find
eyebrow tweezers!
-It was an unfortunate accident.
None of you can
blame yourselves.
-What exactly happened to
your house earlier tonight?
-Naked Monopoly.
-Circumstances
forced me to tell him
the project had been cancelled.
-But you can't mean it, not now.
-It's already been done.
As for you, Mitchell--
-Mitchell.
- --you are suspended
from your duties,
pending an investigation
into your conduct
during the course
of the project.
-And the plot thinnens.
-[laugh]
-I'm Arthur Godfrey
for International
Business Machines.
-Smell the glove!
-Wow, he should have never
played golf with Gerald Ford.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT)
I'm five years old.
-The English Harvey Dent.
-[shout]
--[gasp] I smell
burning eyebrow hair.
--[gasp] I declare this
movie suddenly great!
-[laughs]
-I sense underwear!
[growls]
-Oh, please say it's the
final print of disclosure!
-Oh please, oh
please, oh please.
-Eh, just do a couple
of chin ups here.
-Fab!
-This candy bar's melting.
He's going to have
a hard time being
a Walmart greeter from here on.
-I want me.
-Well, no point of
staying here in the dark.
-I'll be at the security hut.
-It's not dark.
-Cancellation is final.
Nothing more to
be said about it.
But I must impress upon
you both that the work
of this Foundation
is classified.
-There's no need to remind us.
We both signed the
official Secrets Form.
-Yeah, well, I need
to also emphasize
the necessity of keeping
your mouths shut.
-OK, Professor Crabby Appleton!
Geez.
-Now that I've
observed that room.
--[sniffing] I-- I'm
missing "Eastenders."
MAN: Sheila!
-(GRAVELLY VOICE)
Sheila, how's it going?
-It's the Annie Oakley
line of lingerie.
-She tried to buy turtleneck
panties, but they were all out.
-(GRAVELLY VOICE) It's
the hair, isn't it?
-I want you!
I want her, Mike.
-I know, I know.
-It's a kind of
picnic underwear.
-It's wonderful.
-She got that from
the [? ellie ?]
[? mae ?] secret catalog.
-I really do want her, Mike.
In fact, I-- I'm going
up there right now.
-Sit down there.
I don't think you can do that.
-Let me go!
I'm going up there.
-Sit-- sit down.
-I want her.
-(GRAVELLY VOICE) Ah, Sheila,
you've been going heavy
on the scones and lemon
curd lately, haven't you?
-There seems no reason why Dr.
Mitchell and I cannot complete
the experiment, just to show
what success we've achieved,
if for-- for Dr. Steiner's sake.
-A nice sentiment, Dr. Hill.
You assume I notice
the Professor Steiner
himself will not be
able to continue.
-But I didn't mean--
-Don't fool yourself, Blanchard.
He has succeeded.
And what's more,
he could be back
here in his office at any time.
-So drop dead!
-If he retains his
faculties, he will
know there will not
be to much purpose.
-Sometimes you're so
cruel that I think
that you must have
some other motive.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT)
Are you Kim Philby?
-Ms. Anderson is, uh-- she
will think I've forgotten her.
-If there's anyone Sheila can
be trusted with, it's him.
-Yep.
DR. HILL: Oh, that man
gives me the shudders.
-Well, he certainly has
the [? whip hand ?] now.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT)
[? whip hand. ?] Oh my.
I have-- well, I'll have
to ring him up sometime.
Yes.
[? whip hand. ?] mm.
-Yes, England, famous
for its noisy light
switches and telephones.
-Hm, my 2:30 security
guard is here.
-How do you lose a
whole naked woman?
-Oh, I've done it many times.
-Heh.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT) He's going
to take the lorry to the lift.
To the loo.
-Hey, he's not keep that
door closed at all times.
-And this floor must
never be walked on.
[music playing]
-It's Keith Richards again.
-Yep.
-Must have surprised a hedgehog.
-Hey, there's Charlie
Parker's shadow on the wall.
-Oh, yeah.
There it is.
I see it.
-Doodle doo do-do-do.
-We're not up to code!
-[gasp] This repair will have to
be financed through a vigorous
capital improvements campaign!
-There's a part of my
face not covered in fur!
[music trilling]
-Someone's trilling!
-Kelvin?
[inaudible]
-Oh!
[laughter]
-Oh, so the only
colorful thing in Britain
is the throw pillows.
-And their teeth.
-Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
-Yeah.
-There's that, too.
-God, I'm tired.
-I wasn't even asking!
Gee.
What would you like?
A drink?
-Mm.
Yes, please.
-She's dressed like
a Mongolian horseman.
-Is it such a litle while
ago since we've been here.
-It's about four hours.
-Look, are you too tired
even for a few minutes?
'Cause I don't take long.
-Don't look so worried.
We don't know what's happened.
It's not the end of
the world, anyway.
-Oh, for Paul it could be.
-Boy, big headache.
Whoo, big.
-You really are fond
of him, aren't you?
-Of course.
But it's you I love.
-(FEMALE VOICE) Let's
find you a girlfriend.
-I-- I know you're
gonna gag if I do this,
but I-- I gotta
give it a try here.
-Huh, never gotten
this far before.
What's-- what's wrong with her?
-I kiss with all the passion
of a grey Brixton afternoon.
[crying]
-Oh, the horrible aftermath
of their kiss-- oh.
-Who wants an omelette?
SHEILA: Please, let me go!
-Not until you've
answered my questions.
-First, who won the
husband trophy in '57?
-What do you know
about this man Latham?
-But I'm only a secretary!
-Oh, you helped me
once, help me again.
-It's-- it's my eyes.
They're hurting.
-Oh, Sheila.
-Dr. Mitchel though I
ought to see a doctor.
-Oh.
-It's all right, Sheila.
You can use the name.
I know who I am.
Tell me about Latham, then
we'll see about a doctor.
-I want her.
-Well, he spent a lot of
time with Dr. Blanchard,
but no one ever knew
what he was exactly.
-What do you think
he was doing, Sheila?
Spying on us?
-Oh please, Professor,
I don't know.
Truly I don't.
-When I wasn't there, did
either of them go into the lab
without me?
-Diddle I do little lab?
What?
-Yes, wasn't it all right?
-No, it wasn't.
-(GRAVELLY VOICE)
But live and learn.
-How often?
-Several times, most
Mr. Latham by himself.
-Why didn't you tell me?
-It wasn't for me to
question him, Professor.
I thought you'd know.
-Oh, Sheila.
-Please, can I go and
bathe my eyes now?
-Leave her alone.
-Did they ask you to keep
[inaudible] as a secret?
Don't worry,
[inaudible], did they?
-(FEMALE VOICE) Don't
point your diaper at me!
-Well, not exactly.
-Not exactly?
Either you know or you don't.
Which is it?
-Well, Dr. Blanchard
did tell me once that I
was working for the
Foundation, not you.
-God bless you.
-I see.
-Out of one eye.
-All right, Sheila, go
and rinse your eyes.
-Then I can go?
-We'll see.
-A-Again, out of one eye.
-Oh, no, she's gonna
go get dressed!
No, Sheila, don't!
[cries]
[theme music]
-Good morning, Mr. Limpy.
-Oh, we got to see this guy
all post-coital and glowing.
Yuck!
-No.
Sorry, I kneed you in the groin
when you tried to kiss me!
[raspberry]
Would you like some
soggy linguine?
I mean, tea?
-No, don't pour it there.
Ow, oh.
-How long ago did you leave me?
-That's her sexy nightgown.
-Just as long as it
takes to make coffee.
-Yeah, you move too quietly.
-I'll bang around like an elk
if it will make you happy.
-It's cold.
Come back to bed.
-Don't you realize
that it's a new day?
-Called Gablookie Day.
We just invented it.
-There's been no word, then?
-No.
Here, drink your coffee.
I'll telephone.
[phone ringing]
-Oh, they're calling back.
I took the liberty of
ordering you a pump.
-Yes?
-Unsatisfied.
I mean, Betty.
-Oh, Dr. Blanchard.
-Yes, that was us.
Too much squeaking?
Oh, dreadfully sorry.
-Yes.
Yes, as quickly as we can.
-Oh, that's all he can
do, to tell you the truth.
-Something dreadful's
happened at the lab.
-Is it him?
-Blanchard didn't
say, but he sounded--
-Pale, snooty.
- --frightened.
-Bland, detached, British.
-Tell my eyebrows I love them.
-How much longer will they be?
-Any moment, I should think.
-Mm, sorry.
I floated one there.
-[laughs]
-Honk honk.
-Hey, we had sex!
Tell them, honey.
Hey everybody, we had sex and
it was great! [laugh] Sex here.
-That's a British
sport [inaudible].
-Welcome to Euro
Jack In The Box.
DOORMAN: Dr. Hill, Dr. Mitchell.
-I'm Dr. Doorman.
-[inaudible].
So how are you?
Huh.
Well. [whistle]
DR. HILL: [inaudible].
-I am sorry to bring you back.
-We needed help
killing this scene.
-Who were you
expecting it to be?
-We were half expecting it
to be Professor Steiner.
-I see.
-And the other half?
-Now, answer my
questions quickly.
I want my squad here fast.
And until this official Secret
thing's cleared up, I can't.
-Right.
-What was on those computers?
-Porn.
No, wait, no, no.
- --of our experiments.
Where are they?
-That's roughly
what I'm asking you.
-I think he asked rather gently.
-Yeah.
-No, don't touch anything.
-I wasn't going to.
There's no need to
look any further.
These were the tapes.
-No, don't touch that,
or that, or that!
No.
-Dr. Blanchard tells me
you're a pathologist.
-Oh, thank you.
-Till my surgeon
gets here, anything
you can tell me
about how he died?
-Well, at first sight, I
would say electrocution.
-(ENGLISH ACCENT) Oh, at first
sight, I'd say electrocution.
-A man's hat.
-No.
-Well, I think I can.
There's too much for
it to be a coincidence.
I've seen the very
same thing earlier on.
-Pan scam.
Pan scam.
-Well, there's no
possible doubt why
the lights went out last night.
-Somebody's fused
the main power line.
-I know because our beam
is slightly chipped.
-You mean him?
-No, no.
He'd, uh, still be hanging
there, charred to a cinder.
-Well, what about those tapes?
-Rosemary Wood's erased 'em.
-Well, as far as I can
tell, they're all there.
The result of several
years of work in ruins.
-What, do you mean
all your programs?
-Every single one.
MAN: Do you have records, notes?
-Not one.
For security reasons, the
tapes weren't transcribed.
We were going to do it when
the experiment were completed.
-But you could replace them.
-No.
Not without Steiner.
INSPECTOR: Can I get on?
-Well, he's dead, but
knock yourself out.
-Yes, Inspector.
-[sigh]
-If the tapes are
destroyed, then there
is nothing left of
a secret nature.
-What was Latham doing here?
-Fluffing my beard.
-That is for the
inspector to determine.
-Thank you.
-What time did
the lights go out?
MITCHELL: Oh, it was
about 2:15, wasn't it?
-Just about.
-Inspector?
-Inspector yourself!
-I'll be in my office
when you want me.
-Huh?
-Good, good.
-Whoo!
INSPECTOR: Don't
leave the building
without letting me know.
-I had no such intention.
-Tosh, piffery, mommy pots.
-Well, this experiment Dr.
Blanchard was talking about,
the one that brought you
back here last night,
tell me about it.
DR. HILL: Well, we left
Professor Steiner--
--[cries] I miss him
already! [cries]
Perhaps a fresh bow
tie will perk me up.
[phone ringing]
-(FEMALE VOICE) It's the
United States Calling.
A Mrs. Floyd for Mr. Floyd.
-Heh.
-Well.
-And he heads right
for the liquor.
Of course.
-Yeah.
-Let's see, what
would Churchill do?
Ah, yes, get drunk.
-Well, I'll have a screwdriver
without that nasty, bitter
orange juice.
-Yes.
-Geez, is Pablo
Casals in his closet?
I mean, what--?
-[laughs]
-Well, here's to
my leonine hair.
[phone ringing]
-Ah!
Fire!
-Oh, geez.
-It's just the phone again.
They want to make sure Pete
Townsend could hear it,
I guess.
-A "will he get to
the phone scene?"
20 minutes of pure terror.
-Yes?
-President Garfield here.
MAN (ON PHONE): Is
Latham with you?
-If so, you win $500!
-Who's that?
-Where is Latham, Blanchard?
-I asked, who is that speaking?
-I'm an associate.
-Well, I have an
Associate's Degree.
-In fact, you might say
that we are very close.
You understand?
-Stinky, is this you?
[laughter]
-Latham's dead.
-Stinky.
-Then who has the tapes?
-Tapes have been destroyed.
-Hey guys, thinking of
dying my hair orange.
-Whoa, whoa, Mike.
Stop right there.
Careful.
-Stand back, Mike.
Our experiments have given
Crow the touch of death.
-Touch of death, yep.
-What do you mean,
your experiments?
-You know, in
projectednessativity.
You know.
-All right, all right.
You know, call me a skeptic,
but I have my doubts
that Crow has the
touch of death.
-I do so have the
-He does.
-Why couldn't I have
the touch of death?
What, cause I don't have
a diaper on half my face?
Why don't you ever
believe me, ever?
Boy.
-Look what you did.
-Jesus, I'm sorry, Crow,
I was just fooling around.
OK, you have the touch
of death, I'm sorry.
-Ok.
I'm sorry, too.
-Ah.
-I'm a little tense,
and I overreacted, Mike.
I'm sorry.
OK, shake?
-There you go.
-Well, of course, yeah.
-Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, oops.
Huh.
-Huh.
-Yeah, I forgot
for a second there.
Killed Mike.
-Yep, sure did.
Ah, you're going to see
that with your touch
of death and all.
-Touch of death, yep.
Hence, the name,
I guess, you know.
-Death. ---
-Yeah yeah.
-Well, this is
darned inconvenient,
Mike dying like this.
-Yep, yep.
We're going to have to get
him in to watch the movie.
I mean, he can't get in there
himself, that's for sure.
-He, he, he.
Yeah, I guess we'd better
get a head start on it, huh?
-Right, right, right.
A real good [inaudible].
Let's go.
-OK, heave.
-Heave ho!
-Watch out, watch out!
-Oops.
-Darn.
He, he.
OK, here we go again.
-OK, let's give it a try.
Use your legs to lift.
-I don't have any.
-Oh, right, sorry, sorry.
OK, here we go.
-Heave ho!
-Augh!
Augh!
Heave ho!
TOM SERVO: Wait, wait, wait.
I forgot something.
We'll be right back.
Coming.
CROW T. ROBOT: Hey, I
thought you didn't have legs?
TOM SERVO: I don't.
CROW T. ROBOT: Then where'd
you get the foot steps?
I don't quite--
TOM SERVO: Good question.
He, he.
Well, back to it.
Heave ho!
Boy, he's a big one.
CROW T. ROBOT: Heave ho.
Augh.
[theme music playing]
-Wait, he's like a sow.
-He's a big one.
-OK, watch his head there.
OK, ready?
Up.
-You got him?
-Oop, wait, wait.
I almost lost, oop, wow.
-There.
There, that should do it.
-Good job.
Augh.
Wow.
-OK, we're ready.
Let's go.
-All right.
-To finding his way back here.
So why didn't we
try his apartment?
-Hey, three's a crowd, lumpy.
-But I can't stop here.
Someone will be
starting to look for me.
My mum, most likely.
-Don't, wait, no,
we're losing him.
-He's falling over.
-Hang on, get him
up, get him up.
Oh, uh, uh.
-Boy.
Whew.
-Has he taken a liking to you?
-He is my boss.
-That I beginning to understand.
-Mike.
-Curses.
-Oh.
-He's going to nip out
for a case of sure grips.
He, he.
-Don't leave me alone.
-At least give me a
robe or some pants.
-Huh!
-I'm wearing a jock on my face.
What am I doing?
-George Harrison fan club,
could you hold please?
-She escapes and immediately
moves in with Edy Sedgewick.
-Please help me!
Let me out.
Somebody help me!
-Sorry, can't help.
Best of luck.
Stiff upper lip then.
-Somebody help!
-He's going, he's going--
-Here he goes again.
We got to do something
about this, Crow.
Try jolting him again.
-Let's see what happens
if I shake his hand again.
-Augh, oh, ah, ah.
Oh wow, I'm alive, guys.
I died and I've been reborn.
I glimpsed truth, and--
oh, it's this movie.
Goll, grrr.
-Sorry I killed you, Mike.
-I feel a bit better now.
-Good.
-Oh, man.
-You OK?
-Do you know where
Blanchard lives?
-Can you kill me again?
Ah, oh.
Never mind.
-Man, I forgot I had
all this homework.
-Thrill, as he does his taxes.
-The screen explodes with
his light clerical work.
-The hottest typing
and filing of the year.
-I have the touch of
life, too, I guess.
Cool.
-Yeah, appreciate that.
(Singing to the tune of
"walking in memphis")
Walking in Mayfair.
Walking with my darby
and my bumbershoot.
-Ok.
1956 pudding receipts, haggis
bills for the last year.
-No sure grips for this
job, I'm riding bareback.
He, he, he, he.
-Change me.
-Hey, the hair looks great.
-Son.
Stop.
-They paid for the
effect, mind as well
show you the whole thing.
-There.
-Oh, my god.
-Gimme some skin.
Really, I mean it.
Gimme some skin.
-No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, please, no!
No, ah, ah, ah, ah, oh,
hey, my headache's gone.
He, he.
-Huh.
So the lesson I get
from this, Mike,
is to never cut off
someone's research grant
funding without
a proper hearing.
Reconvene the board
and give it the time
and respect it deserves.
-Oh, man, the pudding
goes right to his butt.
Look it, it's just wide as a--
-Old pudding butt.
-Hm, I've never
seen dogs do that.
-Well, if the girl hadn't
stayed unconscious so long,
we might have prevented this.
-Stupid girl.
-After what she said, are
you still in any doubt?
CHRIS: 'Fraid not.
-Who said that?
-Do you know anywhere
else he's likely to go?
-Might have taken the M5
to pounce down on heifer.
-Those people on
the building site.
-I want them.
-Do you think he killed
them accidentally?
-I think he panicked and
just didn't know what
would happen when
he touched them.
-Yeah, I always
kill when I panic.
-As far as I know,
there's no one else
from the foundation
he'll go after.
-No, and he'll probably
try and hole up somewhere.
-Now that his flat's burned out,
could he go back to the lab?
-"Flats."
-No, they're covered.
-Well, we'll just
have to go on looking.
I should imagine
a few frightened
people will soon
put me onto him.
Where will you be?
-At home.
-Oh, right, with your
sex and all that.
Right.
-Just take the
address and telephone
number in case I
have to disturb you.
-Eh, I think I'll head
down to the bank, panic,
kill the branch manager,
take all the money.
-Panic.
-Wow, they couldn't
afford doors,
so they just have handles there.
-He, he, he, he.
-Ah, well then, um,
argh, I suppose.
Argh, what?
Heh, yes.
Um, argh.
Heh, right.
-Sh, man this really bites.
I'm going over to
dark man's house.
He'll understand me.
-I feel so helpless lying here.
-So could you untie me?
-Shouldn't we be
out looking for him?
-No, because that would
be doing something.
-Where would we look?
-Well, they'll call us
as soon as he's located.
-Chris, why did
this have to happen?
-This is actual English sex.
-Blanchard's doing
with Latham behind it.
Paul knew that.
-Well, whatever they
did, they've paid for it.
-She's napping on Big Bird.
-Chris, I'm so
pleased you're here.
I couldn't bear this alone.
-Inspector, thanks to you, too.
-Righto.
-You don't have to.
-Oh, no.
They're going to make
more British people.
-Yuk.
-Grandpa's walking around
outside in his jammies again.
-What a day.
My panic made me methodically
kill 11 people and a cat.
-Son of a gun, I forgot
to go to the store
and electrocute the clerk
and pick up some milk.
-Just get a key made, would you?
-The British
slightly-less-dismal-sex
video series.
-Paul!
-Jump in, Paul.
-How did you get in?
-Argh, look at you two kids.
I love you.
I could eat you up.
-Why didn't you send for
us instead of using Sheila?
It was madness.
-I'm not mad.
-But why use Sheila?
Why not us?
Don't you trust us?
-You dare to ask if I trust you.
-But you can, Paul.
-No.
-You want to destroy me so you
can go on with your lovemaking.
-Why did you come here then?
-Ah, hold on.
I left my galoshes here.
-I need power.
-Don't we all?
-Power to help me think clearly.
-But you can get it
at the lab, while I
program a tape to cure you.
-I'll find it myself.
-Hey, Pink Floyd's
"Animals." "Big man, pig man.
Ah, charade you are."
-Liar!
-I mean, there's energy
discharge that kills people.
-Oh, but I like that.
-I couldn't realign
the laser beam.
The magnetic field
was out of step,
as in the early experiments.
-Paul, I beg you,
do what Chris asks.
-He just wants to get
me out of the way.
-You are out of the way.
-Steiner!
Unless you let us help you,
there's no hope for you.
You destroyed all our tapes
when you killed Latham.
If I can get back
to the lab, I can
begin to program
a reversal tape.
-Oh, and try putting a
light bulb in your mouth.
It'll be funny.
-What can anyone do about that?
-Apew, apew.
-So the cover stick
isn't helping, yah?
-Let him go.
-Can we?
-We must think of a way of
getting him back to the lab.
It's the only way
he can be helped.
-Ah, wait.
What'd I do wrong?
I can't see a damn thing.
-Oh, jeez.
Who's he taping
it to, by the way?
-Good question.
-Ah, he meets John
Merrick on the way out.
Rondo Hatton drops by later.
-Oh, and my trick knee gives
out on top of everything else.
Damn.
-Let's casually discuss
doing some research
on this unfortunate situation.
-Get me Inspector Davis.
This is urgent.
-You can't, Chris.
-What'd she call him?
-I have no alternative.
Inspector Davis?
This is Doctor Mitchell.
-Yes, Dennis' dad.
-I know where you can
find Professor Steiner.
-Shouldn't there be a
pig floating above that?
-Ah ha!
Charade you are.
[theme music playing]
-Oh, well, they're going to see
a performance piece in Soho.
-He's disguised as a door.
-Tonight's episode,
"Foam Side, Death Side."
-Right, we're going in.
Thompson, find out
who's in charge here.
-Sir.
-Tell him what's going on and
tell him to keep these people
out of this section until
I give the word it's safe.
-Right, sir.
-Right.
-And the rest of you, have
you got your special issue?
-Oh, yes, sir.
-At the first sign
of resistance, shoot.
And shoot straight if
you want to keep alive.
-Pssh, pssh.
-Not now, not me.
-You don't mean
to shoot him down?
-If he refuses to be helped,
he'll have to be destroyed.
-But he was so gentle.
-Try to think of him as
he is, not as he was.
Think of him as
the projected man
who has nothing in
common with Paul Steiner.
-Open the gates, we're
going through now.
-Think of him as a man with a
face like a rolled pork roast.
-Ah, [inaudible], don't
take any unnecessary risks.
-Wear a back brace when
transporting a piano.
-There he is.
-(SINGING TO "BAND ON THE
RUN") One guy on the run.
-Bullets bounce off
his face diaper.
-Hey, captain, make
sure you hit him.
-Thanks, Leftenant Obvious.
-Oh, man, I had those
sparklers for lunch.
Oh.
-Go!
-It's no good,
Inspector, bullets
aren't going to stop him.
-Got to go kill a
cat, be right back.
-Drive straight at him.
-Great.
Scotland Yard's elite
hit and run squad.
-Oh.
-Yes, he now has
the power to jog
slowly away from
cars in his pajamas.
-Well, let's let him go.
He'll apply for
another grant soon
and we'll turn it right down.
-Get in the car again.
Keep down.
-So, how's he going
to get power here?
Just put his mouth
on the tap, or what?
-Ah, K, whistle.
Five second violation
on this shot.
-Yeah.
-Inspector.
-What is it?
-If you go in there,
someone's going to get killed.
-Any suggestions?
-I'd like it to be you.
-Somehow, we've
got to persuade him
to come back with us
to the laboratory.
-And how do you
expect to do that?
-Let me go.
I'll get him to come back.
-Don't be crazy.
Look at that.
-Ah, you can't see
anything, but look at that!
-Don't go in there alone.
-Chris, you go back to
the laboratory and start
programming the reversal tape.
The Inspector will
watch out for me.
-I will if he goes with you.
-No, I must go alone.
-And Chris' tenuous
manhood takes another blow.
-Oh, you are whipped, man.
-I'm calling you
out, projected man.
-Paul?
-High plains matron.
-Er, war heroes, come
out and play, hey.
-She rode into town with nothing
but a pantsuit and a side iron.
-Dun, digga dun, digga
dun digga dun dun.
Dun digga dun, digga
-She's pale, she's a matron.
-Come on, pizza face, get
your projected butt out here.
-Ah, he's in there sucking
on car batteries now.
Who knows?
-Paul?
-Paw?
What is this, "The
Rifleman" now?
-Where are you?
-Ah, I found a whole
mess of cats over here.
I'm so happy.
-Paul, listen to me.
Think of all the things
we used to discuss
in our dry and
impersonal British way.
-Paul, you must trust me.
-Please take my
second-party personal check.
-Paul, we can get you face
diapers with more absorbency.
[bang]
-Oh, man, that's annoying, Paul.
-Paul, don't you realize every
time you discharge energy
like that, you weaken yourself.
-Leave me alone.
Go away.
Let me find more power.
-Ball flower?
-Paul, come back
to the laboratory.
Let us work together
to get you well.
-Nothing can help me.
[bang]
-Damn car is such a lemon.
-Paul, why are you doing that?
To frighten me?
-No, I'm just trying to get
the distributor cap off.
It's a bear.
-Chris has gone back.
-Chris.
-Yeah, you know, worked
in your lab and all?
-Is he all you can think about?
[bang]
PAUL: Go away.
You [inaudible] cursed.
You want me to destroy myself.
-Oh, that would
be just smashing.
Thank you, Paul.
-Oh, Charley horse.
Just a minute.
-Yes, great monsters
of the cinema.
Frankenstein's monster.
-Ooh.
-Dracula.
-Ah.
-Paul.
-Paul, I beg you.
Come back to the laboratory.
We can give you all the
energy that you need.
-You promise this isn't a trap?
INSPECTOR: Dr. Hill.
Are you all right?
-Go away.
Keep out.
-I'm chatting up the freak.
I mean, I--
-Shh.
-Look, Paul, I'm tired, too.
I'm going to go back to the car.
You can follow me, if you wish.
-Your random homicides
are beginning
to get me slightly peeved.
-Is that a goat's rear end?
Oh, no, no, it's his head.
Sorry.
-The monster Paul.
-(SINGING TO "ONE TIN SOLDIER")
One thin matron rides away.
-Ba bup ba bum bum bum.
-So now Lembach rides back
into the movie, right?
On a big white horse and Lembach
sings a big production number
and gives everybody grants.
-Yes.
-Why the quail egg
in his eye, anyway?
-If you fuse the switchboard
now, I can't do anything.
Console is programmed
for a reversal process.
-Get away.
It's all over.
Finished.
-Just let me say
goodbye to the rat.
-Oh, Paul, settle a bet.
Did you methodically
kill the three
burglars because you panicked?
We're a little fuzzy on
the panic thing, really.
-What is he doing?
-Ah, he's just doing his
patented head-meltingly
annoying sound effect routine.
-(SINGING) Heard
it in a love song.
-Can't we stop him?
-It's the reversal program.
Projector's become an
instrument of destruction.
Look.
-And it's awesome
destructiveness.
-Yes.
-Argh.
Arg, arg, arg, arg.
-Well, sorry, you guys,
my panic came back again.
-He's projecting at
will now from downtown.
-Paul!
-I am the craw.
-Huh.
There.
Well, this is kind of
an ambiguous ending.
Is this film horrible,
or did it merely suck?
-Yeah, now that I've see it,
should I kick a dog or a cat?
-Do I want the
director just killed,
or should he be tortured first?
-Now, Crow, come on.
-I'm sorry, I just--
-This projector could win.
-The projected world
of Arthur Brown.
-Should we help him?
No, no, no, no.
-Oh, my, what the
world, what a world.
I'm melting.
All my beautiful wickedness.
Who would have thought,
blah, blah, blah.
You know.
-Et cetera, et cetera.
-Et cetera.
Et cetera.
-Makes you hungry, doesn't it?
Ha.
-Crap draft.
[inaudible], not back draft.
-Ah, so the movie and all the
actors in it roast in hell.
-Yeah!
-Oh, that's [? tough. ?]
-So, no more Sheila
in her underwear, huh?
-No, I'm afraid not, Tom.
-Oh, yeah, there's gonna be.
Because I'm going to sit
here, and I ain't going
to budge until I see Sheila
in her underwear again.
And not you, or the police,
or the National Guard
can drag me out of here.
No, no, no.
I don't care if you have
to film scenes over now.
Today, 60 years old,
grandmother of 12,
I want Sheila in her underwear.
-Hold still, Tom.
Hold still.
Just going to give
you your medication.
-No, no.
-Yes, hold still.
-Don't do it,
don't do it, don't.
-There.
There.
Feel better?
-Yeah, I do.
What was in those pills, anyway?
-Bacon.
-Bacon, huh?
Ha!
Worked great.
I feel wonderful.
-OK, it's grant day, everyone.
What do you got for me?
-I'll go, I'll go.
-OK.
-Mr. Nelson, let me commend
your wisdom and prudence
in establishing the Michael
J. Nelson, The Foundation.
And I thank you in advance
for the anticipated approval
for my request of $50, enabling
me to complete development
of a water engine, long
a dream of humankind.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
-OK, whatever.
You got a demonstration for me?
-Oh, oh, right,
right, sure, sure.
If you could pour the distilled
water in there, please.
-Oh, sure.
-Here we go.
Yes, yes.
OK, come on, baby.
Come on, work with me.
Come on, come on.
What?
-Huh.
-Wait, wait.
Hang on.
Did I get distilled water or--
-I guess I don't know.
And we can't fund a
project that doesn't work.
I'm sorry.
-What?
It does work, I tell you.
You're being a fool for
making such a hasty decision.
-Whoa.
-So you have no
interest in maintaining
a cordial relationship with the
Michael J. Nelson Foundation?
-Oh, wait, I'm sorry.
I apologize, Mr. Nelson.
I respect the foundation.
I'm sorry.
-Well, I guess I have no choice
but to fund Mr. Crow and, ah--
-Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I need, ah, $50 to,
ah-- what did I put down there?
Oh, yeah, $50 to buy two
leaf blowers and a hat.
-Oh, well, congratulations.
-Thank you.
-I come to you with
a water engine,
and you give this
slithering fraud
money for leaf
blowers and a hat?
Ha!
I'm sorry, your processes is
painstaking and exemplary.
I'm sorry.
-Mr. Servo, if you
could excuse us,
we are having a
grantee's reception.
-Scram.
-I'm delighted to leave.
Thank you for your rejection.
I'm sorry.
-Let's have a little wine and
then view the foundation's art,
shall we?
-Delightful.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
-Young data hey hey whoah whoah.
Young data hey hey whoah, whoah.
-Paul, T, Mike, I have
reclaimed my destiny.
As a forester, I owe it to the
world to take over the world.
I shall dedicate my
considerable genius
to this and nothing else.
Well, I also do like
those bus trips down
to the dog track outside Omaha.
It's a fun time, and
a really good deal.
And to tell you the truth, I
usually come out pretty good.
I just have a feel for
playing the puppies.
I don't know what--
-Just a tad, you might
want to get back--
Cower, world.
Tremble, world.
Run and kneel, and
puke in terror, world.
Ready?
Harch.
-My cat had two kittens,
I gave them away.
Now I only have
three kittens left.
To the left.
To the left, right, left.
When riding around
in the park you
should always shout
out on your left, left.
Oh my god!
Oh, ooh, oh, ah, he,
ah, ooh, oh he, ah.
[theme music playing]
(Noisy racket in background)
-Lembach is staying in
London for another few days.